Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[person] Yesterday.
the National Intelligence Service
carried out a sudden ambush
at the factory.
Currently. Dr. Jonas's team and the rest
of the researchers are all detained.
The men from the office
are turning the place upside down.
As you suggested. Choe.
we disposed of almost everything.
But the issue is Jonas's team
must have kept one sample alive.
That's what the men from the office took.
[Choe] Yes. Professor. I am aware.
Don't worry. You can rest assured.
I'll take care of it.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
I'll see you at Jeongjinam.
[inhales deeply]
They say good-byes are inevitable.
but I admit this is a bit sudden.
I'm sorry. Director.
We should be the ones apologizing.
Thank you for everything
you've done for us. ma'am.
I remember the first time I saw you.
Director Choe.
I got the distinct feeling that
your superiors were keeping an eye on you.
Looking back at it now.
it seems they always thought of you
as their potential successor.
I'm afraid they may have chosen
the wrong man for the job.
I don't think so.
The men who came before you knew
what they were doing.
If they sacrificed themselves
so that you'd be spared.
they must have had a good reason.
As a matter of fact. I think
you got this far
because you're a man of conviction.
Don't blame yourself.
That's very kind. I'm flattered.
Thank you. ma'am. [inhales deeply]
The late payments.
I'll definitely bring them
to you next week.
[exhales]
That's not what I was implying.
You don't need to worry about that now.
It looks like I won't need
that money anymore.
I already told you I can no longer
provide you with information.
All of our...
antennas have also been cut off.
Head one Japan sent me
a package of the Alligators' handiwork.
I mean. at this point.
there is no place left
for me to run away to.
The last piece of intel we have for you.
The port of entry date and a blueprint
of a portable Swedish-made vault
bought by Head one Japan.
We're short on time.
You're thinking of ending the program?
No. not at all.
I've been keeping track
of their movements.
They will come to us.
As long as they remain concealed.
the contract I have with them is valid.
Whatever happens.
I won't abandon the program.
We will keep going.
[grunts]
[groaning]
[Choe] This...
is gonna complicate things.
Mr. Chae's daughter is quite skilled.
She'll crack it easily.
From what I've heard.
she's mentally unstable.
She has some kind of. uh.
personality disorder.
Dissociative identity disorder.
She has another personality
as her twin brother.
-[thuds in distance]
-[grunting. screaming in distance]
Shit.
[grunting. groaning]
I believe it's time...
[grunts. screams continue in distance]
...for us to bid our good-byes.
-[thud in distance]
-[shout in distance]
[bodyguard 3 grunting. groaning]
[grunts]
[groaning]
[flesh squelching]
THE TYRANT
DELIVERY ACCIDENT
[Mr. Chae's daughter sighs]
Just a little longer and the sun will set.
Since when are days so long in the winter?
Anyway.
life is...
interesting.
Always full of surprises.
[sighs]
How on earth did all this happen?
We found Dad in the parking lot
of the water treatment plant
near Sihwa Industrial Complex.
[tires screech]
[gunshots]
[goon] What do you mean.
"He doesn't know what he's talking about"?
-How does he not know...
-Fuck it... [grunts]
[Mr. Chae's daughter]
I wouldn't have recognized him
if it weren't for the tattoo.
I wonder how they crammed
someone so big into such a tiny bag.
I felt a lump in my throat. for a second.
but I wouldn't say I was particularly sad.
It was bound to happen.
one way or another.
The only thing I regret was that
we were getting ready to retire.
Since Dad was getting on in years.
we talked about running a pub
in Southeast Asia.
Somewhere warm.
Of course. Dad was always right.
He would always say things like.
"Life never goes according to plan.
No one can predict
what surprises life has in store.
Don't be discouraged
if things don't go your way.
That's just how it is."
That's why. back then.
I was willing to let it go quietly.
Back then.
But. now...
[sighs]
Have you eaten?
I mean. Mr. Chae's gone. so that's it.
Let's talk business.
Come to my restaurant. Have a bite.
How's that sound?
[chuckles] Just got some good seonji.
[loud slurping]
[sighs]
Did you need jjajangmyeon
delivered to my haejangguk restaurant?
-[slurps]
-You got no damn manners. kid.
No rush. Take your time.
Yeah.
-[slurping loudly]
-Yeah. take your time.
Here. Have some pickled radish too.
[exclaims]
You okay?
Want something else to eat?
How about jjamppong?
Tangsuyuk is an option too.
If not. you can have some of our seonji.
Mm.
Oh. yeah. [chuckles] Yeah. yeah.
We should talk about work. huh?
[chuckles]
Okay. look. Jagyeong.
I've got a job for you.
It's made in Sweden. [clicks tongue]
It's a state-of-the-art.
portable. handcrafted vault.
It'll be in transit.
There will be high-end security personnel.
A five-to-ten-minute window.
So the job is... [inhales sharply]
...complicated.
[sighs] With Mr. Chae gone.
your hands are the only ones
in this country that can crack it.
Right?
[chuckles]
Also...
[sighs]
Think of it as down payment for the gig.
That's all yours.
[breathes deeply]
I know. okay?
I know it's an insult.
But cut me some slack.
I mean...
Damn it. this is embarrassing as fuck.
But I'm flat broke at the moment. so...
I had to hustle hard to make this happen.
Listen.
Finish the job. I'll double the amount.
Huh? [clicks tongue]
No chance. Forget it.
-Huh?
-Wait a minute.
Why are you calling the shots?
Don't I get a say in this
as your big brother?
-Why do you always decide for us?
-[coughs]
-[thug clears throat]
-Think about it.
Dad told us
not to get involved with moles.
Fuck you. Who are you calling a mole?
You little...
Yeon Moyong.
What's wrong with you?
You wanna die?
No.
I'd rather not.
Right.
Um...
Uh. yeah. I'm sorry. [sniffs]
Okay. I got. uh. worked up a little.
didn't I? [breathes shakily]
[exhales deeply]
Everyone knows you're working
for the office as their mole.
Ugh. Seriously. I'm not. Okay?
Hey.
Rumor has it that you're...
Let's not do this. Hmm?
You... [sighs]
We're both broke as hell. aren't we?
You made all that cash.
but spent it all tracking down his body.
You gotta admit. if it weren't for me.
Mr. Chae's body wouldn't have been found.
We have a history. don't we?
Hmm?
On behalf of your father.
please help me out this one last time.
Hmm?
I'll double the payment
and give you a bonus on top of that.
Hmm. That's enough to retire.
go to. hmm.
Southeast Asia
and open a pub there. right?
Come on. Do me this favor.
Yeah?
-[vehicle engine revving]
-[thud]
[tires squealing]
[agent] Hey. what's happening?
[agent 2] Car four. sitrep! Sitrep!
-[passenger] Hey. no! No!
-[engine revs]
-[cars crashing]
-[tires squealing]
[agent] What the hell?
-Cover those guys!
-[hammer cocks]
-[gunshots]
-[agent 3] Cover Car one! Cover Car one!
[grunts] Behind you!
[gunshots continue]
[agent 3] Take 'em out! Take them out!
Oh. shit!
[thunder rumbling]
[person] Fuck.
Fuck. fuck. fuck.
[muttering]
Fuck!
[groans]
Come out!
Come the fuck out!
Show yourself!
[gunshot]
[exhales deeply]
[choking. breathing shakily]
[gunshot]
Man.
[in Korean] Goddamn. Impressive.
HANGOVER SOUP
[news anchor] Now let's go live to
our reporter on the scene. Ahn Taegeun?
[Taegeun] Yes. I am here
at Chuncheon Dam in Gangwon-do.
[news anchor] And what's the situation
around the Chuncheon Dam?
[Taegeun] Although the storm's intensity
has diminished.
the sky remains filled with thick.
ominous clouds.
Due to extremely heavy rain.
a severe weather warning has been issued.
Because of the rainfall.
as you see behind me.
Bukhangang River levels
are rising rapidly...
-[Moyong slurping loudly]
-[TV broadcast continues indistinctly]
[tapping spoon on dish]
[drops spoon on table]
[Moyong slurps]
Fuck. man. You been fasting or what?
You should try it.
-We only use fresh. high-quality blood.
-[scoffs]
Shove all the fresh. quality shit
down your throat.
What am I doing here?
You know your phone's off?
What the hell is going on?
My phone battery died.
Such an ass.
You are one shitty gangster. aren't you?
Hey.
I don't want this new suit to smell.
Come on. Finish your damn food.
so we can talk.
[news anchor] Na Yeonju.
how much water is being discharged
from Paldang Dam?
[Yeonju] Yes. I am near an area
that is downstream of Paldang Dam.
Right now. the dam is still filling up
with water. from yesterday's heavy rain
that we saw in Jecheon...
[manager] What about the other issue?
[Yeonju] ...places in and around Gangwon...
[sighs]
Do you even need to ask?
[Yeonju] ...1.500 tons of water per second...
-Listen to the news.
-[news report continues on TV]
-Why?
-[sighs]
That dam is releasing
1.500 tons of water per second.
Wow. 1.500 tons.
What would happen if she fell into that?
Think she'd live?
Hey. Make sure you cover your ass.
-The office will identify the body quick.
-[drops spoon]
Ah. Man. you know how long
we've been doing this together?
What are you so freaked out about?
Quit your worrying.
Now. why don't we settle
those overdue payments. huh?
[lighter clicks]
DAMS RELEASE WATER
TO CONTROL WATER LEVELS
[water flowing]
[Jagyeong humming]
[continues humming]
Fuck. seriously.
[sighs]
[continues humming]
[exclaims]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[hostage whimpering]
[driver] Hey. girl.
-I appreciate you working all night.
-[cries]
As for this. we'll put this to good use.
Don't kill me. sir.
You said you'd keep me alive
if I gave you the cash.
-[driver] I was kidding.
-[cries]
You thought I was serious?
Come on. You're an adult.
I won't say a word.
I promise. [crying]
Sir. please. Please don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
"Please. sir. Don't kill me."
Well. unfortunately.
I have to kill you.
So let's make this quick. Would ya?
Don't kill me.
Hey. get rid of her quickly.
and let's go get breakfast.
Shit. I got to take a leak.
[hostage screams]
[hostage crying. muffled]
[chuckling]
[twig snaps]
Oh. shit. What the fuck?
Who are you?
[hostage choking. gasps]
[grunts]
[hostage crying]
The hell. man?
Yo.
-Hey. what happened?
-[driver groaning]
[engine starts]
[groans]
Yo. what the fuck? What the fuck?
Open up!
I said open the door. you little bitch!
Stop the car!
I saw your face. you fucking bitch!
I'm going to kill you. you piece of shit!
You fucking bitch!
[panting]
[breathing shakily]
[hostage screams]
[tires squeal]
[panting]
[groaning]
-[gasps]
-[car engine revving]
[choking. groaning]
DELUXE TAXI
[gangster wheezing. groaning]
Hey.
I didn't give you permission
to take that out.
[continues groaning]
-[flesh squelching]
-[shushes]
[groans]
Hey. I'll do it. Give it to me.
No. you stay put. Brother.
I'll do it.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is something wrong?
[groans]
[gasps]
[hostage crying]
[gangster groaning. crying]
[groaning]
[phone buzzes]
[line ringing]
[person] Hello?
[sniffs]
[sighs]
[politician] An accident
during the delivery?
Yes. sir.
Such refreshing news you've brought me
so early in the morning. huh?
-I'm sorry. sir.
-You think an apology's gonna cut it?
[clicks tongue]
You bastards can take the stairs.
It's only a couple of floors.
Are you sure they were Choe's men?
Yes. sir. He's put together
a black ops team from the opposition.
We're identifying them now.
How far is Director Choe willing to go.
that crazy prick?
He'll try anything
now that he's cornered. won't he?
This is an issue.
Paul. that savage.
will lose his goddamn mind over this.
Get Choe to meet with you here.
Huh?
Choe and me?
-An official summons?
-For God's sake. you idiot.
On what grounds?
We don't have any evidence yet.
You want to get screwed?
By that sly prick?
Don't poke the bear.
You two just have some tea.
We've shown our cards
and it looks like they have too.
Now let's see if there's a way
for us to win.
Out of the way. useless morons.
[sighs]
Have a coffee on me.
I don't drink crappy coffee.
Sure. Planning Committee officials have
such refined tastes.
I get to return to the office this time
like you promised. right?
Stay put and be on standby
until I give you further orders.
[Moyong sighs]
Still on standby?
Yeah. okay.
My team is always just a phone call away.
Tell Director Choe I said hi.
Wait.
Does that dude remember that he's
the one that got me stuck up here?
"Dude"?
Director Choe?
So not good.
Right. "Director Choe."
Watch your mouth. kid.
I'm out.
[phone buzzes]
-Yeah?
-The sample's been retrieved.
Check the contents
and eliminate the team immediately.
The entire field ops team?
[Choe] Yes. the entire team.
I'll take care of the rest here.
[team member] Oh. man.
Let's get ready to go!
We're going off the grid.
So. what happened? Did they get in touch?
Yes. Professor.
-It's all taken care of.
-Oh. great.
Dr. Jonas and his staff members.
They are all unharmed.
Good to hear.
So then. we just need to go into hiding.
Come on. Let's get you to the safe house.
Yeah.
[muffled screams from video]
[groans]
-What the fuck?
-[screams continue]
What do you think?
[caller]
We think what's being developed in Korea
is closer to a virus
than an ordinary serum.
Unlike ours. it doesn't need
to be administered directly to the brain.
It appears it can be activated
through the skin or the mucous membrane.
Fucking idiots.
Why do they keep making shit
that they can't control?
Huh?
I can't say for sure.
but I don't think it was created.
I think they found
something already existing.
[chuckles]
"Already existing"?
[person screaming]
[screaming continues]
[captive mumbling. screaming]
[chuckles]
What's he saying?
He's too far away. I can't hear shit.
He's saying he'll do anything you want
if you just give him a chance.
Just tell him what you want.
No. too late.
I fucking hate useless people.
Cut their heads off. Send them back
to their headquarters for me.
All right.
To Korea.
Got to go clean up their mess.
What's the weather in Seoul?
[screaming continues]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm